[
  {
    "question": "The __________ is a default editor that accompanies Python.",
    "options": { "A": "IDLE", "B": "IPLE", "C": "Text Editor", "D": "Notepad" },
    "correct": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "The __________ is the shell prompt where we type in our commands.",
    "options": { "A": "<<", "B": ">>", "C": ">>>", "D": "<<<" },
    "correct": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "IDE stands for __________________.",
    "options": { "A": "Integrated Direct Environment", "B": "Integrated Development Environment", "C": "Information Development Environment", "D": "None of these" },
    "correct": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "To run a script file code in Python, we can use __________ shortcut key.",
    "options": { "A": "F1", "B": "F2", "C": "F5", "D": "F7" },
    "correct": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "__________ are like words and punctuation marks in English language.",
    "options": { "A": "Literals", "B": "Identifiers", "C": "Variables", "D": "Tokens" },
    "correct": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "__________ are the names given to program elements, such as variable, function, list, tuples, etc. for their identification.",
    "options": { "A": "Literals", "B": "Identifiers", "C": "Variables", "D": "Tokens" },
    "correct": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Literals are the __________ values used in a source code.",
    "options": { "A": "Fixed", "B": "Boolean", "C": "String", "D": "Float" },
    "correct": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "__________ are those identifiers which are used to store values and they allow us to change their value during runtime.",
    "options": { "A": "Constant", "B": "Variable", "C": "List", "D": "Tokens" },
    "correct": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "A comment is basically a text that gives an __________ about the program code.",
    "options": { "A": "Execution", "B": "Compilation", "C": "Explanation", "D": "All of these" },
    "correct": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "We can display program data to the console in Python with __________ function.",
    "options": { "A": "input()", "B": "print()", "C": "output()", "D": "show()" },
    "correct": "B"
  }
]
